juspay.in 2017-02-24

# 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 03, 2015. Juspay Technologies Pvt Ltd. **("Juspay")** is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy **("Policy")** applies to those who visit our website Juspay.in **("Website")** , as well as users of our platform, tools and services offered by Juspay **("Service")**.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at[ privacy@juspay.in](mailto:privacy@juspay.in)

While providing our Services, we may enter into agreements with our Partners/Merchants located within the Indian territory, and provide them access to our Service, which includes the processing of information relating to their customers. Information shared in our Website may be shared with our Partners/Merchants, in order to provide our customers with the Services. We only access such information as reasonably necessary to provide the Service, as otherwise authorized by our customers or as required by law. We are the data processors and not the data controllers of the information. We work with our Partners to help them process payment transactions. 

As the processors of personal information on behalf of our Merchant, we follow their instructions with respect to the information they control to the extent consistent with the functionality of our Service. In doing so, we implement technical, physical and administrative measures against unauthorized processing of such information and against loss, destruction of, or damage to, personal information. 

While we are required to comply with the instructions of our Merchant, we are still committed to protecting the confidential information of our customers, and have adopted this Policy to protect Personal Information. This Policy applies to all transactions involving Juspay, and are in addition to, and not in derogation of, the applicable Terms and Conditions governing our Services. 

This Policy is incorporated in the our terms of use and therefore governs your use of our Services. By visiting the Website and/or utilizing any Services offered by Juspay, you agree to and accept the our terms of use governing your use of the Website and/or utilizing any Services offered by Juspay. 

As a user of the Website and/or the Services, your access to or use of the Website and Services offered by Juspay is conditional upon your acceptance of and continued compliance with this Policy. By using the Website and/or the Services, you agree to be bound by this Policy and all rules, guidelines and/or policies of Juspay, as may be modified by Juspay from time to time, unconditionally and at all times, and further agree and confirm that you consent to providing Juspay with your personal information for the purpose set out in this Policy and you understand that such collection, storage and handling is lawful, necessary and permissible under the applicable laws. 

#### What constitutes Personal Information:

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information shall include:

  * Your Name;
  * Phone number;
  * Residential address;
  * Email address;
  * Password;
  * Financial information such as bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details;
  * Physical, physiological and mental health condition;
  * Sexual orientation;
  * Medical records and history;
  * Biometric information and;
  * Any detail relating to the above clauses, as provided to body corporate for providing service.

#### How Do We Collect, Use and Share Your Information:

We collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, information about the pages that the user accesses on the Website, and information voluntarily submitted by the user of website. The types of information may include your name, company name, email address, telephone number and billing information. The information we collect is used to provide the Service to you, to improve the quality of the Website and Service, to communicate information about the Service. Your information will never be sold to or traded or shared with other companies or organizations for commercial purposes or otherwise, unless we have been expressly authorized by you, either in writing or in electronic form to do so or in a manner as outlined in this Policy. 

Your Personal Information is collected primarily from you. However, we may also obtain information about you from other sources in order to verify the information submitted by you. This verification is primarily done in order to address various security concerns, and to ensure that you comply with the provisions of applicable laws, our terms and conditions of Services available, and other terms and conditions as may be prescribed by us from time to time. 

Juspay may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our Service such as third-party payment processors etc. Transfers to these third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy, and the service agreements with such third parties. 

Juspay collects information on behalf of our Merchant, and has no direct relationship with the individuals with whom our clients may interact using the Service. If you are a customer of one of our Merchants and would no longer like to be contacted by that Merchant, please contact the Merchant that you interact with directly. If Merchant requests Juspay to correct, amend or delete data, we will respond to this request as soon as possible. 

We host and process data, including personal information in Singapore Area, through a third party, to operate and manage this Service. When you access or use our Website or the Service, or otherwise provide information to us, you are consenting, on behalf of yourself and your authorized representatives or end-users, to the processing and transfer of information in and to Singapore which may have different privacy laws from your country of residence. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. 

#### How Do We Collect, Use and Share Your Information:

Juspay's website [or ISP] uses cookies to enable us to retrieve certain information for each visit. Cookies are used in some elements of our site to enable the functionality of that element and ease of use for the user. Third Party cookies, we may use in connection with our Website and the Services provided are: Google analytics and Olark: Website analytics cookie and chat service for visitor information and source. Juspay clients have the responsibility to inform the Merchant with whom they interact with via the help of the Service about the cookies used by Juspay and by themselves and should obtain individualsâ€™ consent, if necessary. 

####  Log Files: 

We may also employ web beacons/web bugs, that help us better manage content on our Website by informing us what content is effective. They are used to track the online movements of users of our Website. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a userâ€™s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. We tie the information gathered by this to our customersâ€™ personal information. 

#### Public/Social forums:

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs and social forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@juspay.in](mailto:privacy@juspay.in). We shall endeavour to remove your personal information, to the extent possible. 

#### Marketing Communication:

Juspay may, from time to time, send you an email regarding the Juspay service or any other services, which we believe could be of interest to you. Only Juspay will send you these direct mails and only if you indicate that you do not object to these offers. You will always have the option of opting out of receiving such mail. 

####  Protection of Information: 

We are aware of the importance of the data we collect from the Website and therefore we use advanced technology to protect such information. We take reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. we will strive do our best to protect your data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at Merchantâ€™s own risk. Your privacy and the privacy of your clients are of utmost importance to us. If you have questions about our security you can contact us at [privacy@juspay.in](mailto:privacy@juspay.in). 

####  Updates/Amendments: 

Juspay reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time for any reason. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. We suggest that you review this policy periodically for changes. The current version of this Policy can be accessed from the link on our homepage, or at the bottom of our other Website pages. You acknowledge that by accessing our Website after we have posted changes to this Policy, you are agreeing to the terms of the privacy policy as modified. 

####  Childrenâ€™s Privacy & Parental Consent 

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children.Please be aware that we have not designed this Website for, and do not intend it to be used by anyone under the age of 18. We specifically request that persons under the age of 18 do not use this Website or submit or post information to the Website. Should we inadvertently acquire personal information or other data from users under the age of 18, we will not knowingly provide this data to any third party for any purpose whatsoever, and any subsequent disclosure would be due to the fact the user under age 18 used our website and submitted personal information without solicitation by or permission from us. 

####  Other Sites 

Juspay is only responsible for the privacy statement and content of this Website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the use of cookies on Websites that you may have accessed from this Website, or the privacy policies adopted by our Partners/Merchants. 

####  Legal Disclosure 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by applicable law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process served on us. 

Your personal data will also be shared between the Juspay services for the activities permitted under this Policy. 

In the event Juspay goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, including an acquisition which occurs as a result of our bankruptcy, the Merchant user account and data will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via [privacy@juspay.in](mailto:privacy@juspay.in) and via a prominent notice on our Website of any such change in ownership or control. 

#### Governing Law

This is an Indian website and is subject to the laws of India. Please note, laws related to personally identifiable information vary from country to country. 

####  No Unlawful or Prohibited Use 

As a condition of your use of this Website, you agree that you will not use this Website or the information or software contained herein for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms and conditions. 

#### Juspay Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your dealings with the Juspay website, you can contact us at [privacy@juspay.in](mailto:privacy@juspay.in). Registered Address: 5C, Zion Cottage, 16th cross street, Indra Nagar, Adayar, Chennai 600020 Current Address: 3rd Floor, Girija Building, #817, Ganapathi Temple Road, 8th Block, Koramangala, Bangalore - 560095 

#### Disclaimer

While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of information offered on these pages, we shall have no liability for errors, omissions or inadequacies in the information contained herein or for interpretations thereof. This Website could include inaccuracies or out-dated information and is subject to change at any time without notice. Your use of this Website is at your own risk. You agree to hold Juspay Technologies Private Limited harmless from and not sue for any claims based upon using this Website. 

THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES CONTAINED ON THE JUSPAY WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. JUSPAY AND ITS AGENTS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE AND SERVICES CONTAINED ON THE JUSPAY WEBSITE, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY MAY LAST, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, TO THE EXTENT INAPPLICABLE. JUSPAY SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL, AS A RESULT OF THE REPRODUCTION, MODIFICATION, DISTRIBUTION OR USE OF THE INFORMATION, DOCUMENTATION, SOFTWARE AND SERVICES. 

#### Links from this website

We do not monitor or review the content of other party's websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or materials appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.
